Heat. Heat.
Oh,
heat, heat.
[Music]
Heat.
Yeah.
Heat. Yeah.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Yeah.
Yeah. Heat.
Oh, heat,
heat.
Yeah.
Heat.
Heat. Yeah. Heat.
Heat. Yeah.
Heat.
[Music]
Yeah.
Heat.
Yeah. Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Yeah.
[Music]
Heat.
Heat
[Music]
up
here. Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
And I also like to
[Music]
mention Heat. Heat. Heat.
manager
special was truly a surprise for me and
my family and
real I'm sure this award will
I'm sure somewhere.
So one day in August
1983, Jerry came
home and
he do this
and start
over 40
years promoting our history and our
culture.
We presented a full art fine art
literature and outreach
programs in
[Music]
2009 without the opportunity to put our
own
[Music]
standal for those of you that don't know
the mission of these artists is to
experience The peace and culture of the
countries that are represented in
the culture
open sculpture is the beautiful mother.
She represents my
mother. She
So the back of this beautiful statue
reads dedicated to all the mothers who
brought their families to America
seeking freedom and a new life.
I appreciate my love for my
home. My
heart and my
sister in
1951 and my love for our culture.
Jerry and I dedicated our lives to
promoting our creation culture and I
will I will continue to you are.
I love
each and our
daughter as well.
So they are my
[Music]
daughter and present school outage
programs.
two of my
[Music]
grandchild. So over the
years to be able to take my
children so that they can see what a
beautiful country is. These are
provided with the opportunity to meet
our
family. The
children
and the
mountains. The exquisite ancient
architecture, the beautiful cathedral
and churches, the lovely green pastures
and
wine and
beautiful
music. I still
have one to
take.
Finally, I'm grateful to the many
wonderful
volunteers over the past 42 years who
each skills and untold powers and with
us here today have
been here. I share this
honor also with those who no
longer
museum
organiz today. I also have with me our
current
[Music]
Heat.
Yeah. Heat.
Maria
[Music]
Patricia
Jerry
and thanks also to
organizations that supported our
projects financially over the
The local
foundation
maration
club business
association
[Music]
family. Congratulations to all the ser
today. Keep on doing everything you do
to promote your culture.
was built by many who settled here and
built into a great
I
warriors in my
heart as
I general
ship. Thank you.